What's this grade-schooler doing here?
R-Raion!
Why are you with these guys?!
Y-You traitor!
Raion, is this kid any good?
Nah, not at all.
Haruto told me what Rights you have.
You'll have no problem taking him.
So that means he's a decoy.
You're an officer like me,
but Haruto treats me like his favorite.
Let's get you a win here so he
gives you the props you deserve.
Raion, you're so...
All right, Omi!
You ready for what's coming?
R-Raion, don't do this!
You should be begging Kai, not me.
I don't wanna die!
You're gonna use your Rights
and put me in danger, aren't you?!
Of course I am.
Huh?
I reject!
Checkmate.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
That's checkmate!
You've been rejected by
the Prime Right of Rejection.
You won't be able to use your Rights
against Omi or endanger him anymore.
Huh?
Now that I've rejected any potential harm,
this is basically a safe zone
and I can protect Raion.
It's practically the Evasion Right!
Rejection Right? He's the owner?!
Raion, what the hell's going on?!
Me joining you guys is all one big lie.
Are you serious?!
You're supposed to be under the influence
of the Negotiation Right, like me!
Your ability to steal Rights with
the Mortgage Right is a big threat,
but the Rejection Right can block your powers.
I'm only here to catch you off guard.
Besides, I don't have any Rights.
So your Mortgage Right
poses zero risk to me.
Raion, why you!
But!
We've got no ammo so... Retreat!
Mm-yup!
What? You've gotta be kidding!
Stop right there!
They're just stalling. What now?
Should I report back to the Emperor?
But His Majesty would believe Raion over me.
And he'd be hurt to know Raion betrayed him.
I'll pretend Raion died in an ambush.
I've gotta kill him myself
and take back his body.
That's for the best.
I see right through your plan.
Prime Right of Superficies!
How did he catch up with us?
Don't you worry.
I'll separate you two
without harming the kid,
then kill you once you're defenseless.
Your only other option is
to fall to your death—
The floor was a screen?!
A trap hole! Damn it!
Nothing beats Gobo's Presentation Right.
All right. I'm off to the next phase.
Roger that. I'll make sure to evacuate.
This is where we get to
the heart of our plan!
Let's see.
We've got some time to spare.
Sure! No one can bother us here.
My space is safe from the Visualization
Right and Transillumination Right.
No one can hear us either.
Nice getup as usual, by the way.
This is the customary gear for magicians.
It's how we hide our tricks and gimmicks.
"Gimmicks," you say...
Does that include the deaths of your friends?
Wasn't there a way to do this without
sacrificing Shinozaki, Souma, or Rika?
Death isn't really all that important.
What's important is me,
Sudo-kun, Raion-kun, Gobo-kun,
and you, Iruga-kun.
Anyone else's death
isn't worth calling a "sacrifice".
Jeez, you can be scary sometimes.
I can hardly believe you're
related to Teppei-chan.
But I like that about you.
So is reconciling not an option?
Unfortunately, no.
When it comes to family,
she loses sight of anything else.
Becoming Queen has only
worsened that side of her,
so I doubt she has any capacity for reason.
I can see that.
It's all for our best chances of winning...
That's what it comes down to.
So?
That vital piece of information...
Is it confirmed?
Of course.
We wouldn't have commenced without it.
Otherwise, we'd be operating
under a different strategy.
You did save one usage
of your Suspension Right
this entire time for that exact reason.
Exactly.
But was this really necessary?
Like I said.
Based on our best chances...
Death is death, and life is life.
The Resurrection Right is in enemy hands.
So death is our best cover
to evade their surveillance.
Makes sense!
They don't seem to be
accounting for the dead.
Whoa!
Since we're technically
supposed to be in battle,
I figured we might as well
leave traces of combat.
Good call.
Then I'll divide things up!
Oops, maybe I overdid it.
I prefer to be more flashy
on the dance floor.
Is it about time?
I'll get going, but before I do...
What's the extent of what you already knew,
and how much of this is speculation?
Who knows? Other than...
Magicians always have tricks
up their sleeve for stage time.
Then I'll leave this space for you to hide in.
I'll make sure the Presentation
Right can reach you.
Good luck.
You too.
They're late. No one's coming back.
Could they still be in battle?
It might be worth using the Recovery Right
to gather bodies just in case.
Raion...
Is he safe? Don't tell me you're dead.
Hey! Haruto!
Raion!
You're safe! Thank god!
They got Kai! And it's not just him!
They got all of us besides me and Iruga!
W-What did you say?!
Iruga secluded Yagihashi
in his space division.
He's checking the area now.
I was able to escape somehow
and met up with Iruga.
Access the Mother Light.
Engage the Rights Cloud.
The Right of Supervision.
He's right. They're all dead.
What about Seraphiel?
He seems to be dead, as well.
The enemies are also lying still,
so I assume both sides perished.
I didn't expect them to take down Seraphiel!
But it's no problem.
Iruga's Division Right can handle them.
Besides, we've got the Recovery Right
and Resurrection Right.
I'll revive them as many times as necessary!
Haruto, recover the bodies and—
Hang on!
They may have expected that and set a trap.
Of course! The Suspension Right!
With Tojuro, it's possible.
Big sis?
Raion, stay with Haruto.
Sure.
Kou, come.
We need to defeat Tojuro
before we can revive anyone.
Can you go out to battle?
If necessary, yes.
I've used the Concealment Right to hide
the Mother Light in the church's basement.
All ownerless Rights are within the Mother.
I can freely extract any Right
with this authorization device.
Just to be safe, can you give me
the Resurrection Right,
and Haruto the Evasion Right?
As you wish.
You're really going, too?
I promise I'll be back.
Wait for me, Haruto!
Raion! I believe in you!
Swear, okay?!
Yeah!
Haruto, you still own the Numbers Right.
We could use Tasuketsu to—
I don't wanna do Tasuketsu anymore!
Big bro died because of Tasuketsu.
The hell I went through
at the Camp changed me,
but I never should have done that.
What I did was wrong!
I wanna look big bro straight
in the eye when he wakes up.
So even if it's just starting now,
I'm letting go of Tasuketsu.
Haruto...
Besides, I wanna believe and wait for Raion.
It's been a long time
since I could believe in someone.
I forgot how good it feels.
You're right. Let's wait.
Raion...
Perhaps the reason you appeared
before us was to save Haruto.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
There! It's Iruga!
Good thing we found each other without issue.
Now let's get back to—
Extended space division.
Iruga?!
Now you're cut off physically,
qualitatively, and perceptively.
I wonder if you can pull from the Mother now?
Too bad I know everything!
You should be more careful of wiretapping.
That's the deal, Kou.
We're taking you down here and now!
I see, so you two were both with the enemy.
But you're wrong.
Re-execution Right
My inherent Prime Right
is the Re-execution Right.
If I trace back my memory,
I can pull any Right from my past.
That Isshiki lady's Prime Right?
You sure brag a lot about hand-me-downs.
I gotta focus on maintaining
this extended space division!
I'm counting on you! Good luck!
Don't worry, Iruga.
I pulled good ones!
Ready, Raion?!
Let's go, Iruga!
Transmutation Attribute.
Prime Right of Scission!
Space division!
That's how you chopped up Yohei.
Scary stuff.
Transmutation Attribute.
Prime Right of Confluence!
Gotcha!
Divide to maximum limit!
Airspace Defense Right!
He blocked it!
We're in trouble if he can
defend spatial attacks.
Deactivation Right.
What?!
He's good.
And most of my focus is on
preserving this extended space.
I may not be able to keep up with this guy.
It'll be over for them
without Iruga's Division Right.
This isn't a whip!
The Prime Right of Falsification
under the Permission Attribute.
The ability to touch objects and falsify
truths about them for five seconds.
In this case, I falsified
the statement "not a whip"
and turned the steel rod
into a whip for five seconds.
I can only falsify one statement
per object at a time.
Aside from life and death, I can
enforce simple state transitions.
That's the rundown, Iruga.
Got that?
And we're using telepathy through
the Right of Communion
under the Permission Attribute, right?
It may come with restrictions, but not bad.
Prime Right
Right
Yeah, considering I just got them...
I'm pretty happy to have these Rights!
Raion Ouno.
Rights unknown.
Then...
Permission Attribute.
Prime Right of Suppression,
My Division Right's vanishing?!
Isolation Right!
Iruga?!
Oh boy. My bad.
I've suppressed his Division Right
and locked him up.
While I have the chance...
I'll kill Raion!
How is this dude stronger than Iruga?!
This isn't a cage!
He's gone.
No.
The ground from this
point forward isn't liquid!
Suppress infall velocity.
It's not working.
That should stop him!
Prime Right of Recurrence.
No way!
Perceptive division.
Closed
Divide the kanji character of "closed".
And that makes the kanji for "gate".
My Right's pretty versatile, don't you think?
What a relief.
Iruga! What's he up to?!
He's trying to deactivate
my extended space division.
So you can only attack
through physical division?!
That's right. Not to mention,
I'll need to hit my target perfectly
if I wanna use my maximum space division.
Airspace Defense Right
Besides, Kou likely owns
the Airspace Defense Right
that used to belong to the Emperor.
It's a Prime Right that
blocks all airborne attacks.
Which means only a mole can
attack him at this point.
Gimme a break!
So our only choice is to attack
from underground?!
Yup.
So? What's the range
of your Falsification Right?
I can activate it within 15 meters
of where I touch the object.
So that's not an option...
Either way, we'll have to stop him first.
I'll go ahead!
Qualitative division.
Divide 100 meters by 100
and transport ahead!
Uh-oh, I was supposed to pass you.
You still suppressing my division powers?
Space division.
Deactivation Right.
Space division!
That should hold him up.
Transmutation Attribute.
Prime Right of Penetration.
Oh boy.
It's no use.
That won't work on me.
You're looking the wrong way.
Divide to maximum limit!
Didn't you hear me? It's no—
A piece of cloth?!
An arm from underground!
Prime Right of Falsification!
Prime Right of Division!
Joint exercise!
Divide to maximum limit!
Divide to
maximum limit!
Impossible! Recurren... ce...
Too late!
"Iruga's arm isn't connected to the ground."
Or so you thought.
That's how it's done!
I was confused when you mentioned
connecting my arm to the ground.
That plan came out of nowhere.
You got the perfect aim, didn't you?
Alrighty then.
We defeated Kou as planned.
You moving on to the final phase?
Yeah. But before that...
Teppei-chan's fifth envelope
of commands: "Love."
Do you still have the envelope
to retain the Obedience Right?
That's right.
It's been safe with me this entire time.
Good to know.
I'm supposed to use this according
to Yagihashi and Sudo's plan, but...
I'm going against their orders.
I know how important this is to you.
So it's only right
that I do this in front of you.
Iruga, I hope you understand.
This is a symbol of my conviction.
I understand, Raion.
I support you.
Thanks, Iruga!
Sudo: Clear
Raion, Omi: Clear
Nishime: Clear
Eren, Hikari: Clear
Looks like we're all ready.
Same goes for me.
Sudo: Clear
Raion, Omi: Clear
Nishime: Clear
Eren, Hikari: Clear
Ryuta, Knight,
Dummy: Clear
Yagihashi:
Now, let's begin turning the wheel of fate!
Suspension Right...
Release all Activations.
Showdown